Sierra Club, Atlantic Chapter; Records apap130
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1967-1998; 4; 13.17 cubic ft.
  - Adirondack Park, Water Quality, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Adirondack Park, Whitney Tract, 1990; 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Air Quality, Acid Rain, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Air Quality, Air Management Advisory Committee, 1992-1995; 3 folders (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9-11)
  - Air Quality, Air Quality in the Adirondacks Conference, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Air Quality, Air Toxics, 1991; 1994; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13-14)
  - Air Quality, Alternative and Renewable Energy Sources, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Air Quality, Atlantic Chapter Efforts, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Air Quality, Automobiles, 1993-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Air Quality, Carbon Dioxide, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Act, 1973; 1981 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Act, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Act, 1994; 3 folders (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21-23)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Campaign, 1974 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Issues, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Issues, 1991; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Air Quality, Clean Air Issues, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Air Quality, Coal-Fired Cogenerator Plant, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Air Quality, CONEG Source Reduction Task Force, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Air Quality, Dry Cleaning, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Air Quality, Electrical Generation, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Air Quality, Emissions and Emissions Trading, 1992-1995; 3 folders (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33-35)
  - Air Quality, Environmental Roundtable, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Air Quality, Fact Sheets, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Air Quality, Global Warming, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Air Quality, Indoor Air, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Air Quality, Legislation, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40-41)
  - Air Quality, Natural Gas, 1988; 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Air Quality, New York City, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Air Quality, New York State Clean Air Act, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Air Quality, Ozone, 1991-1997 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Air Quality, Pollution Control, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Air Quality, Press Coverage, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Air Quality, Press Releases, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Air Quality, Public Health, 1992-1997 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Air Quality, Public Opinion, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Air Quality, Stationary Sources, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Air Quality, Sulfur Dioxide, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Air Quality, Support/Opposition Memoranda From Other Organizations, ca. 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Air Quality, United States Environmental Protection Agency, 1993; 1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Air Quality, Various Items, 1997; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Air Quality, Violations, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Catskill Forest Preserve, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Communications and Media, 1982; 1990-1997 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Earth Day, 1990-1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Economics, Affordable Housing, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Economics, Ecological Tax Reform, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Economics, Free Trade and NAFTA, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Economics, Free Trade and NAFTA, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Economics, Free Trade and NAFTA, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Economics, Labor and Environment Network, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Economics, Labor and Environmental Justice, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Economics, Labor and the Environment, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Economics, Low Wages, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Economics, Maquiladoras, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Electricity, Alcoa, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Electricity, Alternative Energy Sources, 1974; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Electricity, Alternative Energy Sources, 1993-1997; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33-34)
  - Electricity, California Deregulation, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Electricity, Coal Gasification, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Electricity, Community Energy Campaign, 1981 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Electricity, Competition, 1994-1995; 3 folders (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38-40)
  - Electricity, Competition, 1996; 5 folders (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1-5)
  - Electricity, Conservation and Efficiency - Demand Side Management, 1990; 2 folders (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Electricity, Conservation and Efficiency - Demand Side Management, 1994-1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Electricity, Conservation and Efficiency - General, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Electricity, Conservation and Efficiency - General, 1990; 1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Electricity, Electric Mutual Liability Insurance Co., 1997 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Electricity, Electric Rates, 1997 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Electricity, Electromagnetic Fields, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Electricity, Energy Awareness Month, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Electricity, Energy Independence, Declaration of, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Electricity, Environmental Costs, 1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Electricity, Excess Generating Capacity, ca. 1993 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Electricity, Johnston-Wallop Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Electricity, Legislation, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Electricity, New York Power Authority, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Electricity, New York State Assembly Energy Committee, 1995; 1998 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Electricity, New York State Energy Plan, 1991-1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Electricity, New York State Energy Plan, 1994-1996; 5 folders (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23-27)
  - Electricity, Transmission Lines, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Electricity, Undergrounding of Wires, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Electricity, Utilities - Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corp, 1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Electricity, Utilities - Consolidated Edison, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Electricity, Utilities - General, 1993-1996 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Electricity, Nuclear Energy, 1976; 1982; 1991-1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Electricity, Restructuring of Electric Industry in New York, 1997 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Electricity, Siting of Electric Generating Facilities, 1989-1990 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Electricity, Utilities - Inter - Power of New York, 1990-1994 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Electricity, Utilities - Long Island Lighting Co. (Lilco), 1994; 1997 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Electricity, Utilities - New York State Gas and Electric Corporation, 1994; 1996 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Electricity, Utilities - Niagara Mohawk, 1993-1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Electricity, Utilities - Salt City Energy Venture, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Environmental Justice, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Global Warming, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Global Warming, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Global Warming, 1997 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1997 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Brownfields and Voluntary Cleanup, 1992-1997; 3 folders (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6-8)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Cancer, 1994; 1998 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Cement Kiln Dust, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Chlorinated Solvents, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Citizens Within the Ten Mile Radius, 1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Dioxin, 1994; 1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Exposure, 1986; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Hazardous Wastes, General, 1981-1984 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Hazardous Wastes, General Electric, 1997 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Hazardous Waste Treatment Task Force, 1984 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Hazardous Wastes, High - Level Radioactive Wastes, 1995-1997 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Incineration, 1991-1992 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Lead Poisoning, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Hazardous Wastes, League of Women Voters Report, 1986 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Legislation, 1993-1994; 1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Liability, 1991 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Barnwell, SC, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Cortland County, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Disposal, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Emissions, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Export to Russia, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Fact Sheets, 1994; Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Legislation, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Medical Wastes, 1993-1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Michigan Study, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Pataki, George, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Pennsylvania, 1988-1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Permits, 1992; 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Press Coverage, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Report Forms (1 of 2: A - M), 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Report Forms (2 of 2: N - Z), 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Report Forms, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Siting Commission, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Siting Commission, 1992-1994; 4 folders (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4-7)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Siting Commission, 1995-1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Status Reports, 1992; 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Storage, 1991; 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Tonawanda, 1995-1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Transport, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - Ward Valley, CA, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - West Valley, 1982-1988 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - West Valley, 1991 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - West Valley, 1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - West Valley, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Low-Level Radioactive Waste - West Valley, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Medical Wastes, Nonradioactive, 1991 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Mercury Contamination in Food, 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Military Bases, Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Hazardous Wastes, New York State Department of Environmental Conservation Pollution Prevention Memoranda, 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Nuclear Fallout, Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Oil Spills, 1993; 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Papermaking, 1994-1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Pollution Prevention Act (A.8323), 1997 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Polychlorinated Biphenyls (PCBs), 1990 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Polychlorinated Biphenyls (PCBs), 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Polychlorinated Biphenyls (PCBs), 1997; 2 folders (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29-30)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Resource Conservation and Recovery Act, 1991 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Right to Know Laws, 1983-1984; 1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Right to Know Laws, 1992-1993; 1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Schools, 1995-1998 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Soil Remediation, 1991; 1995; 1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Superfund, 1982-1984 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Superfund, 1988-1989; 1993-1997; 4 folders (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7-10)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Toxic Dump Maps of New York State, 1995; Undated (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Toxic Release Inventory (NYSDEC), 1994; 1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Treatment Bibliography, Undated (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Tri-State Coalition for Responsible Investment, 1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Waste Management, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Waste Reduction Regulations, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Waste Site Identification, 1994 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Hazardous Wastes, Zero Emissions, 1995 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Land Use, All-Terrain Vehicles, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Land Use, Billboards, 1993-1994 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Land Use, Clinton Northwest Forest Plan (Option 9), 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Land Use, Conservation Easements, 1981; 1984 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Land Use, Development Rights Transfer, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Land Use, Environmental Facilities, 1995 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Land Use, Environmental Impact Statements, 1991; 1994 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Land Use, Gas and Oil Drilling, 1983 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Land Use, Growth Management, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Land Use, Hudson River Valley Greenway, 1989-1990; 1994-1995 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Land Use, Hudson River Valley Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Land Use, Hunter Mountain Ski Bowl, 1996; 2 folders (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Land Use, Hunting, Trapping, and Fishing, 1992-1996 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Land Use, Land Acquisition and Sales, 1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Land Use, Land Acquisition and Sales, 1990; 2 folders (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34-35)
  - Land Use, Logging, 1974; 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Land Use, Mining, 1990-1997; 2 folders (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37-38)
  - Land Use, New York Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1988-1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Land Use, Northern Forests, 1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Land Use, Open Spaces, 1991-1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Land Use, Open Spaces, 1995-1998 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Land Use, Outings, 1982-1984; 1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Land Use, Permit Applications, 1995 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Land Use, Public Trust Doctrine, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Land Use, Regulations, 1991 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Land Use, State Parks and Other Public Lands, 1967; 1981 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Land Use, State Parks and Other Public Lands, 1982-1987; 3 folders (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48-50)
  - Land Use, State Parks and Other Public Lands, 1991-1993; 1996-1997 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Land Use, Sterling Forest/New York - New Jersey Highlands, 1992; 2 folders (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52-53)
  - Land Use, Sterling Forest/New York - New Jersey Highlands, 1993-1994 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Land Use, Sterling Forest/New York - New Jersey Highlands, 1997 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Land Use, United States Forest Service, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Land Use, Wilderness Protection Act, 1982 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Local Government, Broome County, 1993; Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Local Government, Municipal Officials, ca. 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Local Government, Unfunded Mandates, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated; 5 folders (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8-12)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Board of Directors, 1989-1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Annual Reports, 1964-1967; 1978 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Board of Directors, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, California Convention, 1985-1986 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, California Legislative Director, 1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Centennial of Sierra Club, 1989-1993; 2 folders (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18a)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Chapters and Regional Groups, 1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Committees, 1993 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Eastern New England Group, 1969 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Environmental Bill of Rights, 1995 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Field System, 1997 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Florida Chapter, 1988 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Fundraising, 1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Illinois Chapter, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Inner City Outings, 1986; 1991 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, New Jersey Chapter, 1995 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Northeast Regional Conservation Committee (NERCC), 1982 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Northeast Regional Conservation Committee (NERCC), ca. 1984-1991; 2 folders (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Northeast (Regional) Office, 1987-1989; 1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Northeast Training Network (NETNet), 1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Sierra Club Council, 1986-1989 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, Sierra Student Coalition, 1993 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - National Organization and Other Chapters, State Leglislative Newsletter, Instructions for Creating, ca. 1993 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Other Organizations, Appalachian Trail Conference, 1976-1978 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Other Organizations, Audubon Council of New York State, 1994 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations, Blue Moon Planning Committee, 1991 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Other Organizations, Broome County Nuclear Weapons Reduction Campaign, 1985 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Other Organizations, Catskill Waters Coalition, 1990-1993 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Other Organizations, Center for Policy Alternatives, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Other Organizations, The Environmental Exchange, 1992-1993 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Other Organizations, Environmental Planning Lobby, 1982-1991 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Other Organizations, Henry Hudson Society, 1991 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Other Organizations, Hudsonia, 1997 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Other Organizations, Justice for Farmworkers Campaign, Undated (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Other Organizations, League of Conservation Voters, 1981-1982 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Other Organizations, League of Conservation Voters, 1983-1998 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Other Organizations, League of Women Voters, 1990 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Other Organizations, Letchworth Preservation Alliance, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Other Organizations, Natural Resource Summit of America, ca. 1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Other Organizations, New York Public Interest Research Group, 1991; 1993 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Other Organizations, Scenic Hudson, 1996 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Other Organizations, Toxics in Your Community Coalition, 1988 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Pesticides, Application, 1977; 1981-1984 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Pesticides, Food, 1994; 1997 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Pesticides, Health Effects, 1997 (Box 8 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)